Finding Aid for the Albert Lewin Papers PASC.0314
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2. Motion Picture Projects, (ca. 1954-1991); Boxes 34-41 and 45-53
  - I'll Take Sweden
    - Script, (1964 Jul-Aug) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Negative (The)
    - Treatment, (no date) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Seven Days in Paradise
    - Script, (no date) (Box 39, Folder 6)
      With correspondence to and from Francis Tanzler.
    - Sept Jour Au Paradis - script, (no date) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Script is in French. Also known as Seven Days in Paradise.
  - Wicked Dreams of Paula Schultz (The)
    - Script, (1966 Oct-Dec) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Script materials, (1966-1967) (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Notes and script rewrites.
- Series 3. Television Projects, (ca. 1953-1980s); Boxes 1-28, 35, 37-39, 41, 43, 53, 54
  The Television Projects series contains script materials for produced and what may be unproduced television productions in which Lewin was involved in some capacity. The series is arranged alphabetically into subseries by project titles. The writings include a mixture of complete and partial scripts, notes, story ideas, monologues, outlines, treatments, and occasional production information for television features and episodic series. Projects in the series include Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre, The Brady Bunch, Coffee, Tea, or Me?, The Dennis Day Show, Diff'rent Strokes, The Eddie Cantor Comedy Theatre, Facts of Life, The Ghost an Mrs. Muir, The Good Guys, Green Acres, The Life of Riley, My Favorite Martian, The Odd Couple, and The Ray Milland Show, among others. The files within each subseries are arranged alphabetically by episode title or file titles which reflect the content of the folders. Unless otherwise noted, most files are scripts.
  - Alexander Botts and the Earthworm Tractor
    - Pilot script #9602, (1957 Mar 1) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Script #9703, (1956 Jan 17) (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents
    - Craigs Will, (1959 Dec 17) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alice
    - Story ideas, (1976, no date) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Story synopses for episodes (seasons 1-3), (no date) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - All in the Family
    Work audio tapes in box 62
    - Aunt Lola's Visit, (1977 Dec 15) (Box 1, Folder 5, Box 57)
      Also includes audio work tape.
    - End in Sight, (1978 Aug 3) (Box 57, Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified episode work tapes (Box 58, Box 62)
  - All's Fair
    Work audio tapes in box 58
    - Ideas, (no date) (Box 58, Box 2, Folder 2)
      Also includes audio cassette work tapes
    - Jealousy (folder 1 of 3), (1976 Aug 16) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Jealousy (folder 2 of 3), (1976 Jun-July) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Jealousy (folder 3 of 3), (1976) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Andy Griffith Show
    Work audio tapes in box 61
    - Untitled Pilot idea, (1971) (Box 61, Box 2, Folder 3)
      includes plot ideas meeting audio tape
  - Anna and the King Pilot (Box 60)
    Work audio tapes in box 60
  - Aquanauts
    - Disaster Below, (1960 July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Barefoot in the Park
    - Guess Who's Not Coming to Dinner, (1970) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Marriage Proposal, (1970) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Problem Pooch, (1970s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Rough draft script that may not have been produced or produced under an alternate title.
    - Story ideas, (1970s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Story synopses, (1970) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Includes ASI test results for selected episodes.
  - Barney Miller, 1976 (Box 59)
    Work audio tapes in box 59
  - Big Bluff, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre (also known as Chrysler Presents a Bob Hope Special)
    - Bob Hope monologues, (1964-1965) (Box 34, Folder 19)
      Appears to be monologues created for Chrysler Theater. Originally with file divider labeled Bob Hope Projects.
    - House Next Door (The), (1963 Sept-Oct) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - House Next Door (The), (1967 Aug 10) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - House Next Door (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1960-1963) (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - House Next Door (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1963) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Russian Roulette (folder 1 of 2), (1965 Apr-Jul) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Russian Roulette (folder 2 of 2), (1965 Apr) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Bobby Sherman Show, 1971 (Box 61)
    Work audio tapes in box 58, 60
  - Brady Bunch (The)
    Work audio tapes in box 61 (including Our Son, the Man)
    - And Now a Word from Our Sponsor, (1971) (Box 3, Folder 1, Box 61)
      Audio cassette work tape
    - Eenie, Meenie, Mommy, Daddy, (1969 Jun 16) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Our Son, the Man, (1970) (Box 61, Box 60, Box 3, Folder 2)
      Audio recording work tape
    - Script material and ideas., (1970) (Box 3, Folder 3, Box 60)
    - Underground Movie (The), (1970) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brown Inc.
    - Teleplay, (no date) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - California Fever Telethon work tape, 79 (Box 58)
  - Chico and the Man
    - Root of All Evil (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1977) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Root of All Evil (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1977) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Coffee, Tea or Me?
    - Script, (1972) (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Script, (1972 Sept 28) (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Script-Original Rough Drafts, (1972) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Daley Family #1
    - Treatment, (1957 Jan 22) (Box 39, Folder 12)
      Could be for the motion picture: Summer Love.
  - Dennis Day Show (The)
    - #118 Script, (no date) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Anne Blythe's Surprise, (no date) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Counterfeit, (no date) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Leprechaun (The), (no date) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Medal for Dennis (A), (no date) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Men from Mars (The), (1954 Apr 22) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Party Poopers (The), (no date) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Diff'rent Strokes
    See audio work tapes in box 56,57,58,59
    - Executives (The), (1982) (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 59)
      Audio work tapes
    - Goodbye Dolly, (1978) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Green Hair (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1981) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Green Hair (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1981) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ideas, (1979-1983) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Z, (1983 Oct 13) (Box 6, Folder 2, Box 59)
      Story meeting audio tapes
    - No Time for Arnold, (1978-1979) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - No Time for Arnold, (1978-1979) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Older Man (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1980-1981) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Older Man (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1980-1981) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - On Your Toes (folder 1 of 2), (1981) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - On Your Toes (folder 2 of 2), (1981) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Rivals (The), (1979) (Box 58, Box 7, Folder 4)
      Also includes 3 audio cassette work tapes
    - Will (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1979-1980) (Box 58, Box 7, Folder 5)
      Audio tapes of story meeting.
    - Will (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1979-1980) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Willis' Job (folder 1 of 2), (1979) (Box 58, Box 8, Folder 2)
      Also includes audio cassette work tape
    - Willis' Job (folder 2 of 2), (1979) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - unidentified episode story meeting (Box 58)
      4 audio sound cassettes
    - unidentified episode story meeting (Box 58)
  - Doctor Christian
    - Thin Line (The), (1955 Aug 29) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Donna Reed Show
    - Circumstantial Evidence, (1964) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dora Hall Show (The)
    - It's Dora Hall Just in Time, (1974-1975) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      See also Leave it to Dora.
  - Easier Said Than Done, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Eddie Cantor Comedy Theatre (The)
    - Bargain Hunter (The), (1954 Nov 18) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Call me Irving, (1955 Apr 1) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - How Much for Van Such, (1955 Mar 21) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hypochondriac (The), (1955 May 11) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Lieutenant was no Gentlemen (The), (1955 May 12) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Mink Coat (The), (1955 Jan 19) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Play Pen (The), (1955 Apr 11) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Romance Wrecker (The), (1955 Jan) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco, (no date) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Song Plugger (The), (1955 Jun 21) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Square World of Alonzo Pennyworth (The), (1955 Jun 10) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Suspicious Husband (The), (1954 Dec 20) (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Script
    - Time Capsule (The), (1955) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - What do you want in a Show?, (1955 Jan) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Facts of Life
    - Ideas, (1979 Sept 27) (Box 9, Folder 6, Box 58)
    - Ballet Idea work tape, 1981 (Box 56)
    - Menstruation work tape discussion, 1979 (Box 58)
    - Molly's Holiday, (1979) (Box 9, Folder 6, Box 58)
    - Molly's Holiday (folder 1 of 2), (1979) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Molly's Holiday (folder 2 of 2), (1979) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Farmer's Daughter (The)
    - Uncle Sven Comes to Washington, (1963) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Flip Out with Flip Wilson
    - Script with production information (folder 1 of 2), (1968 Oct) (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Script binder cover removed to box 10 folder 6 for preservation purposes.
    - Script with production information (folder 2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Script binder cover only. Removed for preservation purposes.
  - Flip Wilson Show (The)
    - Flip Out, (1968 Oct 10) (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Also known as The Flip Wilson Show
    - Story Ideas, (1968) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Funny Face
    - Bear Story, 1971 (Box 61)
      Audio cassette work tape (on tape, "troubles with CBS")
    - Work tapes (Box 60)
    - Bigger Than Both of Us, (1971 Oct 28) (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Story outline.
      - Bigger 'n Both, 1971 (Box 61)
    - Holdup (The), (1971) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - M.A.S.H.E.R., (1971) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Repair Man Cheateth (The), (1971) (Box 10, Folder 4, Box 61)
    - Work meeting tape, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Get Christie Love!
    - Frankenstein Connection (The), (1975 Jan 24) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Murder on High C., (1974 Dec 26) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Murder on High C., (1974 Dec 23) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Murder on High C., (1974 Dec 31) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Outlines and Rewrites, (1974) (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Includes material on The Frankenstein Connection and Murder on High C.
  - Getting Together
    - Script (folder 1 of 2), (1971) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Script (folder 2 of 2), (1971) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Ghost an Mrs. Muir (The)
    - Jonathan Tells it Like it Was, (1969 Jan) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Make Me a Match, (1968 Dec) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - My Fair Captain (folder 2 of 2), (1968 Nov-Dec) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ghost and Mrs. Muir (The
    - Release Schedule, (1968-1969) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Ghost and Mrs. Muir (The)
    - Beware of Ghosts Bearing Gifts, (1968 Oct) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Buried on Page One, (1968 Dec) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Captain Gregg Goes to Town, (1968 Jul) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Chowderhead, (1968 Nov) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Dear Delusion, (1968 Oct 10) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ideas and set floor plan, (no date) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - It's a Gift, (1968 Nov) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Medicine Ball (The) (folder 1 of 3), (1968) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Medicine Ball (The) (folder 2 of 3), (1968) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Medicine Ball (The) (folder 3 of 3), (1969 Dec-Jan) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Music Makers (The), (1969 Jan 16) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - My Fair Captain (folder 1 of 2), (1968 Nov-Dec) (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Shooting final script, call sheet, daily production report, first draft script, and rough draft.
    - My Fair Captain (folder 3 of 3), (1968 Dec) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Nobody Loves a Lubber, (1969 Jan 9) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Pain in the Neck (A)- formerly Ghost vs. Guest, (1968 Nov) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Real James Gatley (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1968) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Real James Gatley (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1968) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Son of the Curse, (1969) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Son of the Curse, (1969) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Son of the Curse, (1969 Jan) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Treasure Hunt, (1968 Jun 20) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Vanessa, (1968 Aug 19) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Way off Broadway (folder 1 of 2), (1968) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Way off Broadway (folder 2 of 2), (1968) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Writer's Outlines and Script Ideas, (1968) (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Includes scripts and production material from: Make Me a Match, Not Quite Romeo, I Don't Like Thee, Dr. Fell, and Candy Meets Captain Gregg.
  - Gilligan's Island
    - Coffee Break, (1966) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Goodbye Island, (1964 Jul 17) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Good Guys (The)
    - Art a La Carte (folder 1 of 2), (1969) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Art a La Carte (folder 2 of 2), (1969) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bert's Rufus-In-Law, (1968 Aug 14) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Boy Meets Grill, (1969) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Claudia Sows a Few (folder 1 of 2), (1969) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Claudia Sows a Few (folder 2 of 2), (1969) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Familiar Ring (A) (folder 1 of 2), (1969) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Familiar Ring (A) (folder 2 of 2), (1969) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Honesty is the Worst Policy (folder 1 of 2 ), (1969) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Honesty is the Worst Policy (folder 2 of 2), (1969) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ideas, (no date) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Splitting Headache (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1969) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Splitting Headache (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1969) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - They Eat by Night, (1968 Nov 9) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Good Life (The)
    - Double Life of a Single Wife (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1971) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Double Life of a Single Wife (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1971Jun 18) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Dutton's Retirement, (1971 May 24) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Jane's Double Life, (1971 Jul 6) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pilot work meeting, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Green Acres
    - Boom Town (folder 1 of 2), (1968 May) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Boom Town (folder 2 of 2), (1968 May-Jun) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Ideas (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Grindl
    - Grindl, The Meddler, (1963 May-Jun) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hathaways (The)
    - Foxy Chimp, (1961 Jun, Sept) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Have Camera, Will Travel
    - Pilot Film #2, (1955 Nov 21) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hello Mother, Goodbye -- pilot work tape (Box 62)
  - Here We Go Again, 1971 (Box 61)
    Work audio tapes in box 61 (on item Steve Prtizker)
  - IMP (The)
    - Ideas and Outlines, (1977 Sep-Nov) (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Pilot First Draft and Rewrite Notes, (1977-1978) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1977 Dec) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - It's About Time
    - Which Doctor's Witch? (folder 1 of 2), (1965-1966) (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Which Doctor's Witch? (folder 2 of 2), (1966) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Leave it to Dora
    - Pilot, (1972) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      See also Dora Hall Show.
  - Life of Riley (The)
    - All-American Brain (The), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Aloha, Riley, Goodbye, (1956 Sept 13) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Babs' Dream House, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dudley, the Burglar, (1955 Aug 19) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Getting Riley's Goat, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Gossip, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Homeless Otto, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Juvenile Delinquent (The), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Man's Pride (A), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Oily Birds (The), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Riley Hires a Nurse, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Riley's Allergy, (1955 Dec 15) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Riley's Lonely Night, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Tree That Grew in Brooklyn (The), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Uncle Bixby Takes Over, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - World's Greatest Grandson, (no date) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Young Man's Fancy (A), (no date) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Love, American Style
    - Love and the Human Fly, (1971 Jun-Jul) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Luigi TV
    - Baseball Fan (The), (no date) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Diet (The), (no date) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rumor (The), (1953 Apr 16) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Luigi TV- also called Life With Luigi
    - Eye Witness (The), (1953 May 7) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Many Happy Returns
    - It's a Gift, (1965 Jan 19) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Margie Series
    - Big Movie (The), (1961 Aug 22) (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Brother Brat, (1961 Sept 29) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - County Fair, (1961 Jun 27) (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Margie the Jinx, (1962 Jan, Sept) (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Margie the Matchmaker, (1961 Jun 1) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Marriage Contract, 1972 (Box 61)
  - Maude
    - Ideas, Main Character Profiles, and Synopsis for Tapped Show, (1972, 1979) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Will (The) (folder 1 of 3), (1973 Oct) (Box 20, Folder 13, Box 60, Box 59)
      Box 60: work tapes
    - Will (The) (folder 2 of 3), (1973 Oct) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Will (The) (folder 3 of 3), (1973 Jul-Sept) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Work audio tapes, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Mayberry RFD
    - Sister Cities, (1968 Jul) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Story Ideas, (no date) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - McHale's Navy
    - A Da-Da for Christy, (1964 Apr 13) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - McKeever and the Colonel
    - Blackwell's Folly. Formerly called There'll Always be a Westfield, (no date) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Cookie Crumbles (The), (1962 Jun, Aug) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hair Today, Gone Tomorrow - script, (1962 Sept) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Love Comes to Westfield, (no date) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. Katz, 1971 (Box 61)
  - My Favorite Martian
    - Bottled Martin, (1965 May-Aug) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Doggone Martin, (1965 Jul) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Double Time and a Half, Martian Style, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Grand Theft, Martian Style or The Big Bauble Bobble, (1964 Jun 8) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Has Anyone Seen My Electro-Magnetic Neutron Converting Graitator?, (1964 Jul) (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Horse and Buggy Martin, (1965-1966) (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - How're Things in Glocca Martin, (1964 Oct) (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Martian Fiddles Around (A), (1964 Nov) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Martin and the New Sound, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Martin Goldfinger, (1965 Jul) (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Martin of the Movies, (1965 Jun-Jul) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Night Life of Uncle Martin (The), (1964) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - O'Hara Caper (The), (1965 Sept) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Stop or I'll Steam, (1964 Dec) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Story ideas, (no date) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Story ideas, (1964-1965) (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Tim, the Master Mind, (1965) (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Uncle Martin's Bedtime Story, (1965 Feb) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - My Friend Irma
    - Clyde's Disbarment, (1953 Apr 24) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Nanny and the Professor
    Work audio tapes in box 61 (Witches Brew)
    - Witch's Brew (folder 1 of 2), (1971 Jun, Sept) (Box 61, Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Witch's Brew (folder 2 of 2), (1971 Jul-Aug) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified work tapes, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Needles and Pins
    - Story ideas, (no date) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Odd Couple (The)
    - Fat Farm (The) (folder 1 of 2), (1971 May, Jul) (Box 24, Folder 3, Box 61)
    - Fat Farm (The) (folder 2 of 2), (1971 May, Jul) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Felix Gets Sick (folder 1 of 2), (1970 Jun-Apr) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Felix Gets Sick (folder 2 of 2), (1970 Mar) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Felix is Missing (folder 1 of 2), (1970 May -Aug) (Box 60, Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Felix is Missing (folder 2 of 2), (1970 May) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Felix's First Commercial (folder 1 of 3), (1972 Mar) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Felix's First Commercial (folder 2 of 3), (1972 Mar) (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Felix's First Commercial (folder 3 of 3), (1972 May) (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Felix's Wife's Boyfriend?, (1971 May 19) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Oscar's Birthday (folder 1 of 2), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 6, Box 60)
    - Oscar's Birthday (folder 2 of 2), (1972,Aug-Sept) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Story ideas, (no date) (Box 60, Box 61, Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Where's Grandpa? (folder 1of 3), (1971 Sept, Nov, Dec) (Box 61, Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Where's Grandpa? (folder 2 of 3), (1971 Nov) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Where's Grandpa? (folder 3 of 3), (no date) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - You've Come a Long Way, Baby (folder 1 of 2), (1970 Jul-Aug) (Box 26, Folder 6, Box 61)
    - You've Come a Long Way, Baby (folder 2 of 2), (1970 Nov, Dec) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Oh! Those Bells
    - Forget Me Nuts, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Monkey Sitters (The), (1960 Nov) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Short Change, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Partridge Family (The)
    - Story ideas, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Paul Lynde Show Pilot, 1972 (Box 61)
  - Project planner
    - Lewin commitment chart/calendar, (1971) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Prospectors
  - Quincy, M.E.
    See audio work tapes in box 57,58
    - Story ideas, (1970) (Box 27, Folder 6, Box 58)
  - Ray Milland Show (The)
    - Jury Duty, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Reunion in Comstock, (1955 Jan 10) (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Stratford on the Ozarks, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - TV Story, (1954 Sept 24) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Ring Round Rosie
    - Scripts, (no date) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Roll Out!
    - Command Decision, (1973 Sept) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Honor Truck, (1973 Jul) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Pilot episode, (1972 Dec 4) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Room 222
    - Story ideas, (1968 Sept) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Roosevelt and Truman, 1976 (Box 59)
    work tape with Norman Steinberg
  - Sandy Duncan Show (The)
    Work audio tapes in box 60,61,62
    - Richer the Third, (1972 Jun 6) (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Script- character formerly on the series Funny Face
    - Richer the Third, (1972) (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Character formerly on the series Funny Face. Contains script and production materials.
    - Story Line, (1972 Apr 27) (Box 60, Box 9, Folder 11, Box 61)
  - Stewardesses (The)
    - First draft, (1977 Dec 9) (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - First draft original, (1977 Dec 9) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - First draft, revisions for second draft, (1977 Dec 9) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Outlines and ideas for pilot, (1977-1978) (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Revisions to second draft, (1978) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Script, (1978 Mar 31) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Script, (1978 Mar 31) (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Second draft, (1978 Jan 12) (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Second draft, (1978 Jan 12) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Third draft safety copy, (1978 Mar 29) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Super (The)
    - Story ideas, (1972 Apr 15) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Tales of Texas John Slaughter
    - In the Texas Rangers (Part I), (1958 Apr 11) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Temperature's Rising
    - Story ideas, (no date) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Wavemaker, 1971 (Box 61)
  - West Point
    - Country Boy, (1956 Oct-Nov) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - We're Cruisin' -- Pilot, 1979 (Box 58)
    audio cassette work tape
  - What's Happening!!
    - Movie Maker (The), (1976 Oct-Nov) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified episode work tape, 1976 (Box 58)
- Series 4. Stage Productions, (ca. 1946-1990); Boxes 40- 46
  The Stage Productions series includes script materials for produced and what may be unproduced stage projects in which Lewin was involved in some capacity. The series is arranged alphabetically into subseries by project titles. The writings include a mixture of complete and partial playscripts, notes, and ideas for The Gift Horse and Trashman (which may also be known as The Big Sweat Over Swizel Mahoney). The files within each subseries are arranged alphabetically by file titles which reflect the content of the folders.
  - Gift Horse (The)
    - Notes, (1964 Dec) (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Notes, (no date) (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 41, Folder 2)